[{"question": "  hi!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " so what&#146;s the final head count on my baby shower?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " about twenty, a couple people from work who had something else to do.", "answer": " also both of your sisters called and neither can make it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " what?! you mean they&#146;re not coming to a social event where there&#146;s no men and there&#146;s no booze?! that&#146;s shocking! i don&#146;t care, as long as my mom&#146;s here.", "answer": " oh my god, your mother!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " what?! my mom&#146;s not gonna be here?!", "answer": " well, given that we forgot to invite her it would be an awfully big coincidence if she was.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " my god!", "answer": " well it wasn&#146;t my fault, phoebe was in charge of the invitations!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " well i don&#146;t, i don&#146;t have a mother so often i forget that other people&#133;", "answer": "  oh give it a rest!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " so my mother is not coming to my baby shower?!", "answer": " no.  neither is mine.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " okay, y&#146;know what? don&#146;t worry, okay? we&#146;ll take care of it. we&#146;ll call her. just go home and get ready.", "answer": " please, make sure she comes. it&#146;s really important to me, i mean it&#146;s my mom!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " i know. i know, what&#146;s her number?", "answer": " i don&#146;t know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " go! i have it in my book. go!   wait a minute! if you&#146;re in charge of the invitations why am i the one who has to call her&#151;hello mrs. green! hi, it&#146;s monica geller.", "answer": " oh, hello monica.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": "  hi, umm i know this is last minute, but we&#146;ve decided to throw an impromptu baby shower for rachel today.", "answer": " i know, my daughter&#146;s told me about it when they received their impromptu invitations a month ago.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " yeah, i&#146;m sorry. i&#146;m-i&#146;m so sorry.", "answer": " for what dear? for not inviting me or lying about it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": "  oh my god, my ass is sweating!  please! please! can you come? it&#146;s today at four.", "answer": " well all right. i&#146;ll see you at four.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " isn&#146;t it at three?", "answer": " son of a bitch!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " hey joe! you wanna shoot some hoops?", "answer": " oh no, i can&#146;t go. i&#146;m practicing; i got an audition to be the host of a new game show.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " oh cool!", "answer": " that&#146;s great.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " yeah-yeah, and if i get it by day i&#146;ll  dr. drake remoray, but by night i&#146;ll be  joey trrrribbiani!", "answer": " you&#146;ll be perfect for this! that&#146;s already your name!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " but the audition&#146;s in a couple hours and i don&#146;t even understand the game.", "answer": " well do you want some help?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " oh really? that&#146;d be great! you guys can be the contestants!", "answer": " awesome!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " okay, i guess we can lose to junior high girls some other time.", "answer": "  all right! let&#146;s play bamboozled!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " bamboozled?", "answer": " yeah, isn&#146;t that a cool name?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": "  yeah!", "answer": "  no!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " all right. uhh, okay. our first contestant is ross geller. why don&#146;t you tell us a little something about you ross?", "answer": " well uh, i-i&#146;m a paleontologist. umm, i-i live in new york. i have a son ben. uh, hi ben!  and uh&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " i said a little bit ross. now, how about you chandler?", "answer": " well joey, i&#146;m a headhunter. i hook up out of work soviet scientists with rogue third-world nations. hi rasputin!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " excellent! let&#146;s play bamboozled! chandler, you&#146;ll go first. what is the capital of columbia?", "answer": " bogota.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " it&#146;s ba-go-ta, but close enough. now, you can either pass your turn to ross or pick a wicked wango card.", "answer": " what does a wicked wango card do?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " i should know that. let&#146;s see, just one moment please. umm, here we are, a wicked wango card determines whether you go higher or lower.", "answer": " higher or lower than what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": "  can you believe how lame this is?", "answer": " i&#146;m sorry, i don&#146;t believe contestants are allowed to talk to each other.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " oh, i told the stripper to be here at five. that&#146;s good right?", "answer": " you ordered a stripper for the shower?! that is totally inappropriate!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " what? he&#146;s gonna be dressed as a baby!  oh hi mrs. green!", "answer": " hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " i&#146;m so glad you could make it.", "answer": " yes, thank you so much. and again, we&#146;re so sorry. we could not feel worse about it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " she&#146;s still mad.", "answer": " yeah i know. isn&#146;t it great? one less person we have to make small talk with.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " phoebe, sandra&#146;s mad at you too. it-it doesn&#146;t bother you?", "answer": " no look, we&#146;ve apologized twice! i can&#146;t do anymore than that. i know you hate it when people are mad at you but you just have to be okay with it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " look at that face! just like when you were in high school! if i didn&#146;t know better i&#146;d say you were a cheerleader in trouble. come on, let&#146;s get some tea.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " oh my look at that. only three weeks to go, now have you picked your nanny yet? now i don&#146;t want you to use your housekeeper &#145;cause it would just split her focus.", "answer": " oh well actually gonna use a nanny and uh, i don&#146;t even have a housekeeper.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " it&#146;s like you&#146;re a cave person. rachel, you must get a nanny. you don&#146;t know how overwhelming this is going to be. i mean when you were a baby i had full time help, i had mrs. kay.", "answer": " mrs. kay! oh yeah, she was sweet. she taught me spanish. i actually think i remember some of it, tu madre es loca.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " such a sweet woman.", "answer": " well, however great she was i just can&#146;t afford that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " oh rachel!", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " i just had the greatest idea! i&#146;m gonna come live with you!", "answer": " wh-wh-what? what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " oh, i&#146;m so happy i&#146;m gonna do this for my little girl. aw, look at you. you have tears in your eyes.", "answer": " yes. yes i do.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " all right ross you&#146;re in the lead, would you like to take another question or spin the wheel of mayhem?", "answer": " the wheel has not been my friend tonight joey. uh, i&#146;ll take another question.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " okay, this is gonna be tough. hold your breath.", "answer": " it&#146;s okay, i&#146;m ready.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " no dude, you gotta hold your breath until you&#146;re ready to answer the question.", "answer": " this is ridiculous, he&#146;s not gonna hold his breath&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " okay, what do you have a fear of if you suffer from this phobia, tris&#133;holy cow, that&#146;s a big word. trisc&#133; seriously look at this thing. chandler, how do you say that?", "answer": " let me see that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " triscadecaphobia.", "answer": "  the fear of triscuts!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " no! no, fear of the number 13.", "answer": " fear of triscuts?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " it&#146;s possible, they have really sharp edges.", "answer": " all right chandler, you&#146;re up.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " wait a minute, i-i believe i&#146;m entitled to use my angel pass for a free turn?", "answer": " this game makes no sense!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " y&#146;know what? you&#146;re just upset because you&#146;re losing.", "answer": " oh come on ross, i think we&#146;re all losers here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " all right. chandler, you can either spin the wheel or pick a google card.", "answer": " let me think. let me think&#151;oh! i don&#146;t care.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " you-you must choose mr. bing.", "answer": " either, it makes no difference.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " choose, you jackass!", "answer": " i&#146;ll take a card.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " okay, you picked the gimmie card! you get all of ross&#146;s points!", "answer": " what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " this game is kinda fun.", "answer": "  you don&#146;t think it&#146;s a little crazy that you get all my points just &#145;cause you&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " why did you invite my mother?!", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " she wants to move in with me and ross to help take care of the baby.", "answer": " for how long?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " eight weeks. i mean i love my mother, but my god, a long lunch with her is taxing.", "answer": " i personally would be honored if she wanted to live with me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " she can&#146;t hear you.", "answer": " what? you guys, come on! what am i going to do?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " well, if you don&#146;t want your mother to move in with you, just tell her.", "answer": " you&#146;re right. you&#146;re right. i mean i&#146;m about to have a baby, i can tell my mother that i don&#146;t want her to just be sleeping on my couch! oh my god! she&#146;s gonna want to sleep in my bed with me. this cannot happen!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " that&#146;s right. that is right, you go over there and tell her you don&#146;t want her to live with you. do not take no for an answer!", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": "  this is great! now she&#146;s gonna be mad at rachel! y&#146;know what? and i&#146;m just gonna swoop in there and be like the daughter she never had.", "answer": " i have new respect for chandler. all right everybody! it&#146;s time to open the presents!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " yes! yes! and i think that the first gift that rachel opens should be from the grandmother of the baby, because you&#146;re the most important person in this room. and in the world!", "answer": " well uh, i don&#146;t have a gift because i wasn&#146;t invited until the last minute, but thank you so much for bringing that to everyone&#146;s attention.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " mom that&#146;s okay that you didn&#146;t get you a gift!", "answer": " well, i kinda did. me. eight weeks of me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " oh yeah. okay, see mom, the truth is i can do this on my own.", "answer": " sweetheart i know you&#146;re gonna be terrific mom, i just think you need a little help, especially at the beginning.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " but mom, i really know what i&#146;m doing. i can handle this.", "answer": " really? remember twinkles?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " he was a hamster! i am not going to vacuum up my baby!", "answer": " okay, come on rach it&#146;s present time! y&#146;know you&#146;re the glue that&#146;s holding this whole party together. it&#146;s kinda falling apart here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " oh look.", "answer": " wow!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " okay, this is from your friend at work.", "answer": " oh my gosh! oh wow! oh, i know what this is!  wait a minute. that can&#146;t be right. is that a beer bong for a baby?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " darling, that&#146;s a breast pump!", "answer": " did i say i was done guessing? okay, thank you for that. oh wow! what&#146;s this?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " it&#146;s a diaper genie.", "answer": " oh, it dispenses clean diapers!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " no! it&#146;s where you put the dirty ones!", "answer": " well that&#146;s gross, why don&#146;t you just take it outside and throw it in a dumpster?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " oh you&#146;re gonna do that ten times a day?", "answer": " what?! it goes ten times a day! what are we feeding this baby?! indian food?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " no dear, that&#146;s what babies do.", "answer": " rachel, listen to your mother. she is very smart.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " plus, what are you planning on doing with the baby while you&#146;re trotting out to the garbage ten times a day?", "answer": " i don&#146;t know, i&#146;d leave it on the changing table?  what?! what&#146;d i do? what&#146;d i do?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " you can&#146;t leave a baby alone!", "answer": " oh come&#151;&#151;of course i know that. i mean of course you never leave a baby alone! i mean who would&#151;she wouldn&#146;t be safe as she would be with me, the baby dummy. oh god, okay. y&#146;know what? i think opening the presents right now is a little overwhelming right now. so i think umm, i&#146;m just gonna maybe open them a little bit later, but thank you all for coming. and for these beautiful gifts, and this basket is beautiful.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " it&#146;s actually a bassinet.", "answer": " okay mommy, don&#146;t ever leave me.  commercial break", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": "  in what john houston film would you hear this line, &quot;badges? we don&#146;t need no stinkin&#146; badges!&quot;", "answer": " treasure of the sierra madre!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " correct! there&#146;s a possible backwards bonus!", "answer": " madre sierra the of treasure!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " yes!", "answer": " i&#146;d like to go up the ladder of chance to the golden mud hut please.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " wise choice, how many rungs?", "answer": " six!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": "  that noise can only me one thing.", "answer": "  hungry monkey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": "  hungry monkey!  haaa!  i&#146;d like a wicked wango card!", "answer": " okay, it&#146;s an audio question, name this television theme song.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": "  oh.  oh! oh my god! okay, i know this, give me-give me a second!", "answer": " tell it to the time turtle!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " shut up! i dream of genie!", "answer": " yes! yes, you&#146;re back in the lead!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": "  oh come on!!", "answer": " all right! all right! uh, umm, super-speedy speed round!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " is there a hopping bonus?", "answer": " of course!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " who invented bifocals?", "answer": " ben franklin.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " correct! which monarch has ruled great britain the longest?", "answer": " queen victoria.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " correct again! but, you forgot to switch legs between questions, so no hopping bonus!", "answer": " noooo!!! every time!!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " now, over to chandler.", "answer": " i&#146;d like a google card.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " are you sure?", "answer": " yes!  no!  google!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " oh my god! congratulations ross, because chandler, you&#146;ve been bamboozled!", "answer": " nooo!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " yeah!!", "answer": " this is the best game ever!!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " so umm, you&#146;re gonna stay with me as long as i need you?", "answer": " of course i am!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " oh mom, i swear i&#146;m not an idiot. i&#146;ve read all kinds of books on pregnancy and giving birth, but i-i just didn&#146;t think to read the part about what to do when the baby comes. and-and then guess what? the baby&#146;s coming and i don&#146;t know what to do. oh, can i throw up in my diaper genie?", "answer": " no. sweetie, you&#146;re gonna be fine.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " wait-wait where are you going? where are you going?", "answer": " i&#146;m going to the bathroom.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " now don&#146;t worry! everything&#146;s gonna be okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " it is going to be okay!  it was worth a shot.", "answer": "  hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " hey! why are you all red and sweaty?", "answer": " i just bamboozled chandler!  which is not uh sexual thing. that was a quick shower.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " not if you were here.", "answer": " wow! it looks like we got a lot of good stuff.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " oh we did, but my mom got us the greatest gift of all.", "answer": "  a play-dough barber shop?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " no. she&#146;s going to live with us for eight weeks.", "answer": " uh, what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " what&#151;you&#146;re not serious. i mean she&#146;s a very nice woman, but there is no way we can take eight weeks of her. she&#146;ll drive us totally crazy.", "answer": "  hi ross!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " hey joey, hi! i&#146;m ray; i&#146;m the producer of the show.", "answer": "  it&#146;s a pleasure to meet you ray.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " and this is duncan  and erin, they&#146;re gonna help us out with the audition. so uh, let&#146;s get the camera rolling.", "answer": "  rightie-o ray!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " whenever you&#146;re ready.", "answer": "  hello, i&#146;m joey tribbiani! let&#146;s play bamboozled! erin, you get the first question! in hockey, who is known as the great one?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " wayne gretzky.", "answer": " correct! now, would you like to pick a wicked wango card or spin the wheel of mayhem?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " uh joey, didn&#146;t your agents give you the revised rules? we&#146;ve eliminated all of that. no wheel, no cards.", "answer": " what&#151;why?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " uh well, the game was too complicated and research showed people didn&#146;t follow it.", "answer": " well what&#146;s complicated? you spin the wheel of mayhem to go up the ladder of chance. you go past the mud hut through the rainbow ring to get to the golden monkey; you yank his tail and boom! you&#146;re in paradise pond!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " yeah all that&#146;s gone. it&#146;s basically just a simple question and answer game now.", "answer": " well what&#146;s fun about that? you expect me to be the host of a boring game that&#146;s just people standing around answering questions?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " well, there&#146;ll be women in bikinis holding up the scores.", "answer": "  let&#146;s play bamboozled!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " &#133;and all those dinosaur nick-knacks you have ross, i thought they might be more at home in the garage.", "answer": " well we&#133;we don&#146;t have a garage.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " did i say garage? i meant garbage.", "answer": " y&#146;know what? maybe, mrs. green, it&#146;s not absolutely vital that you live with us.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " well rachel needs help with the baby.", "answer": " i do. i really do. i don&#146;t know anything.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " i&#146;m-i&#146;m sure that&#146;s not true.", "answer": " oh no? pheebs? monica? do i know anything about babies?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " no, not a thing.", "answer": " it&#146;s frightening.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " well uh, y&#146;know what? even if she doesn&#146;t know anything, i do! i have a son. and his mother and i didn&#146;t live together, and whenever he was with me i took care of him all the time, by myself.", "answer": " that&#146;s true. you do have another child.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " with another woman. have you no control ross?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " that&#146;s a different issue. uh, the point is, when the baby comes i will be there to&#133;to feed her and bathe her and change her. and more than that i want to do all those things.", "answer": " well then you really don&#146;t need me to live with you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " yes! yes, you&#146;re gonna be so missed.", "answer": " you&#146;re gonna be a great father.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " hello?! i still don&#146;t know what the hell i&#146;m doing!", "answer": " oh, come on, every first time mother feels that way. you&#146;ll&#151;you&#146;re gonna pick it up.  hey! you will! uh look, y&#146;know when you first came to the city? you were this spoiled helpless little girl who-who still used daddy&#146;s credit card. do you remember?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": " i hope you&#146;re going somewhere with this.", "answer": " look at you! what&#151;you&#146;re-you&#146;re this big executive! you are much more capable than you give yourself credit for. i-i have no doubt you&#146;re gonna be an incredible mother.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": " really?", "answer": " i&#146;m telling you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 269, "asentId": 270}, {"question": " all right you two, i&#146;m gonna get going.", "answer": " oh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 273, "asentId": 274}, {"question": " oh no-no-no-no sweetheart, you stay put. i&#146;ll let myself out. it&#146;s like i&#146;m not here, which i almost wasn&#146;t.", "answer": "  you&#146;re still so funny. you&#146;re so funny.  what do i do?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 275, "asentId": 276}, {"question": " nothing! you have apologized to her like a million times and she&#146;s been nothing but terrible to you. and don&#146;t forget you just threw her daughter a lovely, albeit slightly boring, shower, and she hasn&#146;t even thanked you for", "answer": " y&#146;know what? you&#146;re-you&#146;re right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 277, "asentId": 278}, {"question": " yeah i mean if you want to say anything to her, i&#146;d tell her off.", "answer": " really?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 279, "asentId": 280}, {"question": " uh-huh!", "answer": " okay! i will! mrs. green? mrs. green!  it is rude to leave a party without saying good-bye to the host! yeah, and-and also when someone apologizes to you the decent thing to do is to accept it! now what i did to you, it wasn&#146;t on purpose! but what you&#146;re during to me now is just plain spiteful!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 281, "asentId": 282}, {"question": " spiteful?!", "answer": " that&#146;s right! maybe it&#146;s time you took a good hard look at a mirror young lady&#133;old lady&#133;lady!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 283, "asentId": 284}, {"question": "  wrap it up, wrap it up, wrap it up&#133;", "answer": " so whenever you&#146;re ready to apologize to me, i will forgive you. good day!  i can&#146;t feel my legs!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 285, "asentId": 286}, {"question": " you were fantastic! i&#146;m so proud of you!", "answer": " yeah? i&#146;m proud of me too.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 287, "asentId": 288}, {"question": " you should be!", "answer": " yeah could-could-could you get me something to drink?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 289, "asentId": 290}, {"question": " you got it!", "answer": " okay.  mrs. green! okay i&#146;m really sorry!! i&#146;m apologizing for the&#151;  okay, i bit my tongue, but i&#146;m still really sorry!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 291, "asentId": 292}, {"question": "  okay! i&#146;m ready.", "answer": " you sure?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 293, "asentId": 294}, {"question": " yes, i&#146;ve done my studying and i really know my stuff.", "answer": " all right then.  rachel green! let&#146;s play bamboozled!  how do you test the temperature of the baby&#146;s bath water?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 295, "asentId": 296}, {"question": " uh, put your elbow in it.", "answer": " excellent! how do you put a baby down for a nap?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 297, "asentId": 298}, {"question": " full, dry, on its back, and no loose covers.", "answer": " that&#146;s correct! this is an audio question, what do you do when the baby makes this sound?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 299, "asentId": 300}, {"question": " check if it&#146;s wet, check if it&#146;s hungry, burp it!", "answer": " excellent! excellent, now-now do you want another question or a wicked wango card?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 301, "asentId": 302}, {"question": " a card! a card! i pick a card!", "answer": " oh, i&#146;m sorry you&#146;ve been bamboozled! you&#146;re gonna be a terrible mother!  i&#146;ve lost sight of why we&#146;re doing this!  end", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 303, "asentId": 304}]